

# VITALII NAUMENKO Frontend Developer

E: vitaliy\_\_naumenko@ukr.net

P: +380960803451

L: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vitalii-naumenko-69860a104

A: Kyiv, Ukraine

#### **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS / PreprocessorCSS

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

React.js

GraphQL

**TWIG** 

**Tailwind** 

Bootstrap

### **LANGUAGES**

Ukrainian - native

English - intermediate

## **PROFILE**

Front End Developer with 5+ years of experience executing with plethora diverse skills. Enjoy working closely with team members to ensure workloads are effectively. With a passion for both personal growth and for software development. Ready to apply my passion for coding to a talented developers team to develop quality solutions.

## **EDUCATION**

Information Security | Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics Sep 2008 - Jul 2011

# **EXPERIENCE**

EasyPay | Front End Developer, Kyiv

Feb 2022

- Worked with product and back-end teams to create web product.
- Architected product tours with React for a new feature that improved customer.
- Migrated a multi-page user experience into a single page app which improved customer engagement.

NDA | Front End Developer, Kyiv

Jun 2020 - Nov 2021

- Development and implementation of new modules and support current functionality.
- Partnered with data science to develop the front-end for a product recommendation engine that increased user time on page.

NDA | Front End Developer, Kyiv

Apr 2018 - Oct 2019

- Designing and developing features to meet customer requirements and business goals.
- Building high quality and highly reliable software to meet the needs of the product owners.
- Writing clean, elegant, and reusable code that solves complex problems.

WD & SS | Front End Developer, Kyiv

Jun 2017 - Apr 2018

- Developing websites for internal project design management.
- Identified and implemented dynamic web solutions in line with company standards and best practices.